Mokku, witches come out on nights like this. You must never go outside.
A witch?
That's right. On full moon nights like this, the witch who lives in the Enchanted Forest comes out to kidnap children.
What does she do after kidnapping them?
She drinks their blood.
Their blood?
Yes.
That is why children must not stay out late playing.
That's a lie. It's just a story grownups made up to stop kids from going out.
It is not made up!
The witch in the Enchanted Forest is a vampire.
Come on now, Mokku, go to sleep.
I'm not sleepy.
You're a good boy, aren't you, Mokku?
Keep that up and Grandpa won't help you if the vampire comes and carries you off.
How boring.
See? You're sleepy after all.
Boring, so boring. I wish school didn't exist. I hate school!
Now, now, stop grumbling. Time for bed.
You need to sleep early so you can go to school. Otherwise, the witch will come kidnap you!
I'm a puppet! Why would she ever kidnap me?
That's right. Grandpa just can't help treating me like a real human child. Good night.
I want to become a real human, too.
Good morning!
Good morning, Mokku! Did you do your homework?
Oh no, I forgot!
You'll be made to stand in the hallway again!
Yeah... me neither...
I hate math, too!
Me too. Mama said a witch would come out last night, so I was terrified... / Me too! I was so scared!
Scaredy-cats. Witches aren't real.
I watched the street all night. The only person who passed by was old lady Koshiki.
But Grandpa said so. He said witches live in the Devil's Forest. And vampires, too.
That's just superstition. I bet you were shivering in bed, praying to God.
I don't believe in witches either.
I just thought if I told the teacher that, he'd forgive me for the homework.
Then let's go explore the Devil's Forest right now.
If we go to school, they'll just make us stand in the hallway anyway.
Still... Mokku's just scared of the witch after all.
Mokku is a chicken!
I promised Grandpa I'd go straight to school!
Fine! We're not playing with a coward like you anymore!
Let's go!
Yeah!
I'll go too!
(Good night)
Mokku, don't go!
Shut up!
Real courage means going to school!
Mind your own business! I'm not a coward!
If you go to the Devil's Forest, you'll regret it!
Out of my way!
He's completely hopeless...
[[MUSIC]]
I misjudged you, Mokku. There's no way witches exist.
Besides, I'm not scared at all!
The foot of that mountain is the Devil's Forest.
I'm starting to get scared.
If there's a witch, I'll catch her. We'll make a fortune putting her on display.
We'll be top-rate showmen. We'll take the whole world by storm!
Rosanna, what do you want to do?
I don't want to go.
Right. We've never come this far from home before.
Mokku, let's go back.
We came all this way!
Suit yourself. But I said no girls allowed!
Let's go.
Yeah.
Come on, Mokku. Let's go home. Everyone is worried.
I'm a boy. I'm not going to be a coward.
What's the matter, Mokku? If you're scared, go home with the girl.
Wait! I'm coming! Hey!
Lino, you go in first.
Marco, you go first.
No way. Franco's supposed to be first!
Tch, look at you shivering.
You're shaking too, Franco!
I'm just trembling with excitement!
I'll go.
No child who ever entered that cursed forest has survived. May God protect them.
All right, move out once you're ready!
Wait!
What is it?
What are you doing here?
Please, take me with you.
An old geezer like you would only slow us down.
He is my beloved grandchild. Please!
I said no, and that's final.
All right, let's go, everyone.
Take this. Put it on the end of a stick, and thrust it at the vampire if he appears.
Dear God, please protect me.
Franco!
Gino!
Mama!
So close!
Damn it!
Franco!
Help me!
I just want to die... Damn it!
Franco!
You're safe now. Daddy is here. / Papa... Papa, I'm sorry.
What happened to Mokku?
Lino!
Marco!
(Ghostly sound)
Hah!
(Ghost screech)
What did you come here for?
A-Are y-you a w-w-witch?
Quite a feisty one, aren't you? As if there would be witches in these woods! (laughs)
Mokku is my only reason for living. Dear God, please save him.
Old man!
Where's Mokku? What about Mokku? Is he safe?
No! That can't be! It can't be!
Both Lino and Marco were eaten alive by wolves.
My boy was the only one who managed to survive, but...
It was my fault... "Study, study"... Forcing Mokku when he hated studying so much... Mokku, please forgive me...
Be naughty, be lazy, be selfish, it doesn't matter! My boy, please just come back to me!
Really? No school or church, and we can just play from morning till night?
That's right. This is a paradise for lazybones.
I love the sound of that!
Climbing trees, catching birds... I hate studying!
Is that so?
I'm so glad I met you, granny.
Are you now, are you now? You're a good boy.
Look over there, see?
Wow, a castle! Can I really live there?
[[NO AUDIO]]
It's pretty, but why are there only red flowers?
Countess Leonard loves the color of blood. Hmm?
Hello there! I'm Mokku. What's your name?
These little people can't speak at all.
Come along now.
Incredible!
Countess Leonard...
I have returned.
Good work. What is it?
It looks like the Oak Tree Fairy.
The Oak Tree Fairy?
Yeah, she's like a mother to me, but...
The Countess is much prettier.
Oh, thank you.
Then I shall be your mother from now on. / Really? I'd love that!
Of course. I adore children, after all.
The other children were wearing crosses, so even the wolves... Poor things... / Do you mean Franco and the others?
No, just some foolish children.
I'm not foolish!
I know. Come along. Let us go to my room.
He was my husband, and the lord of this castle.
He's dressed funny.
Yes, he passed away a very long time ago.
My family died out 500 years ago.
500 years ago? Then how old are you, Countess?
I am 521 years old. / What?!
521 years old?!
I'm the prince of the castle! I'm a prince! A prince!
I'm a prince! A prince!
(Sobbing)
Honestly, that Mokku is completely hopeless.
Grandfather hasn't eaten a thing all day and has been worrying sick...
Please get some rest.
He's not a human child.
You are not a human child.
Go sleep with the dwarfs.
(Laughter)
[[NO AUDIO]]
[(LAUGHTER)]
Hey, let's play, everyone!
Why are you working so hard?
We're allowed to play from morning till night here, right?
Oh, I see. You can't speak.
Look, heave-ho!
See? Isn't it fun?
You guys try it too! Come on!
Come on!
Something's strange...
Just when I thought I could finally suck the blood of a healthy child... There isn't a single drop of blood in his body, only water.
I have a good idea.
Mokku!
Yes!
What is it, Mama?
Don't you want some friends?
Yes, I want to be friends with the dwarfs, too.
The dwarfs won't do. None of them can speak.
So bring children from the village. Yes, a cute girl would be nice. You must have a girlfriend or two. / I sure do! Let's see... Anna, Rosanna, and Sophia? I'm surprisingly popular.
Bring them all here. And make sure they take off their crosses. / Why?
You hate school and church too, don't you, Mokku?
Mama hates kids who go to church, too.
Yeah! I'm on my way!
Good. Make sure you bring them.
(Laughter)
Mokku, now wherever you go, you will obey my every command.
Now, go!
(Laughter)
[(LAUGHTER)]
Bewitched and completely hollowed out inside, Mokku obeyed the vampire's orders and lured his friends behind the forest.
At last, the long-awaited blood of healthy children is his to drink.
The vampire finally reveals his terrifying true form and prepares to attack the young girls.
What will become of Mokku and his friends?
Tune in next week for Kashi no Ki Mokku!